Are you French?
>> See, I can tell. I can [__] tell just
by the way you looked at me with your
[__] little attitude. Look [laughter]
at that [__] Look at that [__] He's
crossing his legs. You look so gay, but
also you have a girlfriend. I was like,
"This guy must be French." Yeah. No, but
the way you cross your legs, dude. It
just It is offending me deeply. Like you
[laughter]
like literally, dude, he's like I don't
know. You do this French thing where
you're like with a little French toe,
[laughter] you know? You're just like,
"Oh, another joke my boy.
Come on.
Oh, the French people, man. People
always say French is such a sexy
language, which I think it can be sexy,
but also to me, sorry, no offense, man.
Actually, no, let me offend you. It is a
to me, French, it sounds a little like a
little slow, like you have a speech
impediment. They're always like
bucket. It's like, what the [__]
[laughter]
Do you want a coloring book? Like what
the
>> Oh, the French people. Oh my god.
>> That's Stella Arto. That's a [__]
>> That's yours. Oh, you say Artoa. Sorry.
>> Shut the [__] up. You [laughter] say No,
no, no. You don't say. How do you say
how how do you say the beer?
>> Really? [laughter] What the [__] is
wrong with y'all? But you cannot
pronounce folks vagen properly.
[laughter]
But then the [__] French words you
pronounce correctly, dude, that pisses
me off. That's crazy. For me, when I
first came here, I always ordered a you
know, and then the barista looked at me,
he was like, "What do you mean you
[__] [__] That's how you say it." I
grew up speaking French, you know. So
now when I try to be more American now,
now when I go to the coffee place, I'm
like, "How do y'all could I please get
one of them one of them gay bagels?"
Yeehaw. [laughter]
I'm learning. My wife shows up to the
car 25 minutes late.
[laughter]
What is the laughter about you [__]
[__] Yeah, you guys must be Latinos.
This is unbelievable. Yeah, there's no
way these are Germans laughing. Yeah,
this is not a place for laughter. Yeah,
this is a comedy show. Leave your house
outside. No, this is serious. She was 25
minutes late. Yeah. Where are you guys
from? [laughter]
[cheering]
>> Ah, Brazil. Yeah. Do you live in Germany
or do you live in just visiting?
>> I live in Germany for 7 years.
>> Seven years, brother. And have you still
what's your name?
>> Ricardo.
>> Ricardo. Oh, you say it's so sick. I'm
fully hard right now.
>> Ricardo. Germans don't do that [__]
Nobody says I'm g people are hard turned
on. Ricardo.
>> So, Ricardo, how are you with time
management and punctuality [laughter]
>> in German? Sol.
>> Sol. Yeah, look at the lack of
specificity is a problem. Yeah. Uh,
Ricardo, I think we're going to have to
do something about this. We're going to
send you to the little punctuality camp
and uh hopefully you will be on time.
Yeah. Do you have German friends? Is
somebody with you or are you with
another late Brazilian?
>> My wife is German.
>> Oh, your wife is German. So, what
happened? Have you become more Brazilian
as a result? Have you been
>> She's like, "No,
>> it's not that bad. That sounded racist.
You you I thought I was going to get
cancelled for like racist. I think you
are the problem here." Yeah. [cheering]
She's like, "Did you become a little
Brazilian?" NO. NO, NO, IT CAN'T HAPPEN.
How do you guys meet?
>> We work in the same company.
>> And at the company, they don't care if
you're on time or not. [laughter]
>> You should work for some good German
government position. I recommend you
work for the
And then maybe,
dude, do you know there's a place? It's
so funny, dude. Like I looked up what I
is or German like news station number
one. There's a big building here near
Brun Gate. I was walking past there.
Bill asked me like, "Hey, what does RD
stand for?" And I looked it up and I was
like, "Oh, Bill RD stands for
[laughter]
I was like, "What the [__] [applause]
That is crazy." And what's your excuse
for being late, Ricardo? He acted out
for me. Last time you were late, I'm
your German boss or friend. And I was
like, Ricardo, why are you late once
again? And then what do you say?
>> The last time I was actually late for my
wedding. [laughter]
>> [cheering]
[laughter]
>> Ricardo. Uh,
Ricardo. Uh, nobody likes you here,
Ricardo.
We all hate you, Ricardo. You made
something impossible happen. We like you
less than the French people. And, uh,
you made the impossible happen. Yeah.
Just say what you want about the French.
They are pretty on time. You guys seem
like a beautiful couple though. But what
is what is your name?
>> Jacine.
>> Jacine. Are you French?
>> No. [laughter]
>> No. No.
French.
No.
>> It's cool. I think you'll be punished by
the next joke I'm going to make. Uh,
just remember, you know, I don't know
why. Uh, so now my wife was 25 minutes
late and she had no remorse. I've been
waiting here for 25 minutes. You know
how much work I can get done in 25
minutes as a German. Yeah, dude. In 25
minutes, Germany could score six goals
against Brazil.
[cheering]
[__] [__] you. [__] you. [cheering]
Oh my [__] reticard though, man. I
knew I was going to do that joke and I
was like I was hard the whole time. I
was just like I was just [laughter] I
was just precoming literally waiting for
the moment. I was like when it happened
a beautiful and then we all came and it
was unbelievable. We all So Ricardo,
where were you when Germany uh
Um, so for those who don't know, I mean
most of you do know probably Germany
wants to be Brazil 71 in the World Cup
semi-final. It was unbelievable. And
every day I'm whenever I'm sad a little
bit and when it's gray outs, I watch
that video and it gives me joy. It gives
me Shaden Floyd, which is [laughter]
the joy you feel from seeing somebody
else suffer. Whenever people asked me,
hey, what is shenan? What is the joy you
feel from seeing somebody else suffer? I
was like, just watch that video and
watch these Brazilian kids fall apart.
Yeah. And cry. and women crying and all
this stuff and when you watch that you
feel a little sad but also a little bit
of you feels a little bit excited. Yeah.
You feel you feel a little tingly. Yeah.
That is what the sh is. Yeah. And then
you you you have to let it overtake you.
Yeah. No. But seriously, how was that
for you?
[laughter]
>> You know how 911 is for the
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I know. I know. I
know. Yeah.
Yeah. But you know 911 was only two
towers. It was seven for us. You know
what I'm saying?
Oh, imagine, dudes. Imagine you're in
Brazil in just like seven airplanes.
>> Yeah. No, that's crazy. So, who do you
watch it with? I'm very curious about
this, guys. We're going to spend 20 more
minutes on this cuz I'm I'm a little uh
Yeah,
>> I was in Brazil and it was a family
barbecue. So,
>> barbecue.
>> Nice. That's amazing. Yeah. So, how was
everybody reacting? Who was there? Was
your mom there? Stuff like that.
Were they just completely like just
shocked or did they fully crumble, fall
apart? Did they have rage? Did it turn
sexual? What happened, dude? I want to
know. [laughter]
>> My mom literally cried.
>> Nice. I love it.
[laughter]
>> Do you happen to have a video of that
moment,
man? I like this moment a lot. Thank
you, Ricardo, for coming to the show.
Yeah. [laughter]
Yeah. You know what, Ricardo? Let's do
this. After the show, can you come back?
I mean, also your wife. We're not going
to make it a sex thing, but like you
should [laughter]
you should come. I have a consolation
gift for you, okay? So like come
backstage later. I'll give you
something. Yeah. Um [applause]
yeah, yeah, yeah. You guys see about the
Kanye West tweets?
>> Dude, I had the busiest [__] month of
my life, dude. Because I've never seen
anything crazy like this. I mean, except
for Elon doing a full perfect hit two
times just a week prior.
Listen, it's been a busy week for a
German. Yeah, [laughter] I looked at the
the tweets and they're really dicey.
They're dicey tweets. Yeah. One tweet he
said. It's the first one I saw. My
friend sent them to me. I I love Hitler.
Space space. Now what, [__]
[laughter] And it's really hard for me
to see this as a German because I'm just
I'm just really angry at the fact that
there is absolutely no punctuation, no
capitalization,
no grammatical order at all. Yeah. It's
just a space in the middle. What the
[__] You know what I [laughter] mean?
Like, if you want to be a Nazi, you also
should be a grammar Nazi.
[laughter]
Dude, if Hitler saw that, he'd be
furious. Yeah, absolutely. It is no
grammar here.
This should be Listen, and I fully
distance myself. I fully disagree with
the message, but in a grammatical
correct sentence, this should be I love
Hitler. Full stop. What now? [__]
question mark. Yeah, that I can respect.
But this is a [__] disgrace. Yeah.
Unbelievable. You [__] Yeah. Yeah. They
should ban him for that from from X.
Yeah. That's right. Spreading mis
grammar information is the worst thing
he do. He does. [laughter]
And then this is [__] crazy. Also,
it's so ironic that he's like Hitler so
fresh. He's like Hitler's biggest
fanboy. Hitler would be pissed if he
knew that. You know what I'm saying? Cuz
also, dude, Connie is black and Jewish.
Do you know what I'm [__] saying? He
it's so he'd be the first one on a
little train. Yeah. Back then it's
[laughter] crazy. They would not like
him, Connie. They would not like you,
dude. They would hate you. What the
[__] man? Hitler, I think if if Hitler
saw what what what Connie is doing, he
would I think he would be distancing
himself, too. He was like, "Oh, Connie,
is this tone it down a little bit with
the anti-semitism?" Yeah. A little bit a
little bit too much. Yeah. Yeah. I don't
know why Hitler always has a gay voice
in my actouts, but [laughter]
it just feels more manageable, you know?
He's like, "Cany, come on. This is a
little too much." Yeah.
I tried [snorts] to make videos today
about the whole thing and I was like
where do I even there's like he tweets
like as a German I got to say the whole
seeing those tweets of Kanye West being
super anti-semitic. It was it was weird
for me to see and I just I'm just
puzzled as a German by how efficiently
this guy tweets. I mean so many it was
like
unbelievable. Like I couldn't do that
[__] If I wanted to I couldn't do it,
man. That's unbelievable. He tweets
faster than a Meta Spence assembly line.
That's crazy. [laughter]
It just keeps going. What the [__] He
tweets like blitzkick. Yeah. [laughter]
And it's true.
And and now we're all like all of us
were like, "What the [__] is happening
to us?" He tweets so much. He's [__]
I now know how Polish people felt in 90
39. [laughter]
>> It's true. That came so quick. I don't
know what's going on.
>> Did you ever find out?
Oh my god. just made me think of that.
Oh, that's really problematic. I should
think about that. So, there's a what do
you call musical chairs, right? How do
you call musical chairs? Just musical
chairs.
>> [__] This is a problematic thing. It
just occurred to me that musical chairs
in German is called the journey to
Jerusalem
where you have a bunch of chairs lined
up like a train
[laughter]
and then if you don't get the train fast
enough you will be eliminated.
[laughter]
But at the end of the game everybody
gets eliminated except for one person.
So that's another thing we should be
very guilty [clears throat] about. Uh,
[laughter]
[__] That's [__] up, dude. That's a
true story. I never thought about this.
Well, thanks for making me more guilty
than I already am. Now I'm going to have
to pay for another one of my wife's
weddings. Uh, [laughter]
she's going to be like, "Oh, there's
another one. Another Chanel for me.
Thank you."
>> I don't know how to say the car brand's
full name for BMW. Can you clarify
[laughter]
>> who wrote this?
>> Me.
>> You seem scared. [laughter]
Rightfully so. Yeah,
>> it's BM and not BMW.
>> Well, okay. How do you when you see the
car outside on the street, how would you
say, "Hey, look, it's a nice
>> beamer."
>> What? [laughter]
A beamer?
>> No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Keep
going.
>> You leave the show right now. A beamer.
A beamer. Like a like a projector.
A beamer. It's a respectful card that
demands the respect. Yeah. Do you What
car do you drive?
>> The Camry. [laughter]
>> The Camry. Good. Good. Cuz I'm glad you
could. You don't you don't deserve a
[clears throat] German car. Yeah.
[laughter]
>> I hate this. I hate this. When
Americans, they're also they're driving
the car and they're like, "Oh my god, I
just bought a BMW. It's such a
disrespect." Yeah. It's unbelievable.
Yeah. It is B MV.
>> Yeah. BMV. It stands for
So [laughter] very slowly, you have one
chance right now.
Can you say it right now? What is the
car name?
>> Can you repeat it? [laughter]
[laughter]
What?
>> It's worse than I thought. I think I
think you should not only not have a
BMW, we're going to take your Camry from
you. Yeah. [laughter] You should not
have a car. Give me your keys right now.
You're not allowed to drive anymore.
Yeah. This is it now. Now give me your
keys now. You're Polish, right? I mean,
obviously. Yeah. No, clearly. I mean,
yeah. This [laughter]
This is also a Polish. It says Pska. And
then there's an eagle that looks exactly
like the Nazi eagle. This is crazy. So,
like, how do you call Poland? Is it the
motherland?
>> I don't really think we have an We don't
really like have like anything. Yeah.
No, I know. You guys were invaded a lot.
That's [__] up, man. Yeah. Poland is
like the Buffalo Bills of Europe. You
know what I'm saying? [laughter]
[laughter]
I knew he was going to like that. How do
Polish people feel about Germans? Do you
all have some resentment or is it like
>> more knowledge and more history? We have
an understanding.
>> Yeah, cuz do here's the thing. Jewish
people I love saying that word cuz
people get very tense immediately.
[laughter]
So the Jews be like, "What the [__] is
going to happen next?" No, they come to
my show so much and I love it, right?
And I really wonder why. Like it's like
maybe it's like some sort of Stockholm
syndrome, but I love it. Yeah.
[laughter]
>> I watched one of your YouTube videos.
>> Yeah.
>> You said,
>> "Oh god,
dude. I [__] hate the crowd I've
cultivated, man. This is [__]
horrible." You know, you guys are the
most opinionated [__] You know what I'm
saying? My comedy show and my audience
is like, "Listen, you were late." Yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> You didn't get the cards on time.
[laughter] Now we're going to come to
your comedy show where people are
supposed to laugh to lecture you about a
mistake you made. Okay, [laughter] man.
Polish people got to put them in their
place. Dude, [__] This is horrible.
Yeah, I'm kidding. No, what did I say?
>> You said that Volkswagens are actually
superior to Audi's. Audi's are
considered lower class in Germany and
Porsches are the highest class.
>> Yeah.
>> Why do you not like Audi's? Why are
Audi's lower than Volkswagen? Volkswagen
makes them their luxury version.
>> Wow. You seem to be very insecure about
your Audi. [laughter] Very I'm just
asking like why do you think Audi is
inferior to the Volkswagen? Yeah. I'm
just asking you. You must have a small
dick though. This is unbelievable.
[laughter] You're like I told you. I
told you. Why do you think my car that I
have and has you dude? Who has a
keychain hanging on their white pants
just hanging there? Have you seen his
dick?
>> Never seen his dick.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm only going to continue if you show
us your dick right now. Show us your
dick. [laughter]
No, I think he's that close to actually
doing it. No, it's not going to go down
now. And I don't recall saying that
because I think Audi is truly a little
bit above Folkswagen. Yeah. So your dick
can relax a little bit. Okay, we can
relax. Yeah. Folkswagen is like the
basic car like what people have like
whatever like a Honda Civic or something
like you know based line Volkswagen Golf
is the most common car in Germany and
then Audi is a little cooler but maybe
not quite where Mets would be. Okay. And
oh god dude this is [__] hilarious
man. [laughter] Germans don't get
offended by anything but once you talk
about that [__] about out cars then the
Germans come to life. You know what I'm
saying? So what's your opinion about the
story? You had a very strong emotional
He hasn't said a word the entire show by
the way. I have not heard a sound from
him. And in that moment HE WAS LIKE
WHAT? HE JUST like could not contain
himself. Okay.
>> Well, no. I think Mercedes is definitely
a good car, but Audi is definitely more
the fun car. More youthful.
>> More youthful. Yeah.
>> You know, allwheel drive, bad weather
and snow.
>> I love this. Give me a full [__]
essay about the difference between Yeah.
What's your thought on on Matas then?
So, you think Matas is like the
>> I think it's appropriate for like more
older people.
>> Okay. Okay. [laughter]
>> Yeah. So, like wealthier people, older
but not as cool, not as youthful. And
then BMV is for the Armenians.
[laughter]
Trump is saying that there's too many
German cars in America, right? He's
complaining about that. He's saying
there's not too many Chevrolets on the
outban.
They get car sick. You know what I'm
[laughter] saying? You can't have that.
Yeah, that's one thing I miss. People
often ask me, "Hey, what what do you
miss about Germany?" I miss the German
bread. Superior. Like no question about
it. Food quality in general. But then
the Altaban, the no speed limit is
incredible. I took my friend Jeff to the
Altaban in Germany and he was so scared.
And I was driving, you know, we're not
going that fast, like maybe like um 200
km or something, you know, and then
[laughter] uh and then he was so scared,
you know, he was like, "Oh my god, bro,
I can't believe you guys have no speed
limit on the autoban. Isn't that so
dangerous?" I was like, "Jeff, I can't
believe you guys had guns at Walmart."
Everybody [laughter]
like,
>> I think the autoban is way safer than
any middle school in America. Okay,
we're good. [laughter]
You know what I love about French
people? No matter where I am in the
world, when I make fun of French people,
it brings people together. And that is
[laughter]
such a beautiful thing you guys do. No.
How do you feel as a French guy? Would
you agree that some of French people are
a little country? Yeah. [laughter]
>> It's a stereotype.
>> In Paris? Yeah.
>> In Paris? Oh, where are you from?
>> PARIS. [laughter]
>> I mean, it's the more direct up front.
>> Yeah.
>> So, people take it as
>> No, no, no, no, no, no, no. You
[laughter]
more up front, dude. Like, okay. I tried
I I went to France, right? And I speak a
little bit of French. And when you try
to speak French, they don't give a [__]
They always have to make you feel bad.
You know, if you go to France to cafe,
you're like, "Uh, bonjour, could I
please get a a croissant?" Then you see
there some French dude is just like him.
You know what the [__] French dude is
going to be [laughter] like?
[laughter]
It is not called croissant. It is called
Jesus [__] Christ. Okay. Could I
please get a No, no, no, no, no,
[laughter] no, no. IT IS NOT QUASO. IT
IS CALLED AWESOME. It's like Jesus
Christ.
You know, it just keeps going. Cuz
you're basically saying, what you're
saying is that just because your country
historically does something, you're
going to keep going with that and not
try to change. Yeah. Imagine we Germans
did that. [laughter]
Imagine we Germans were like, "Listen,
we've always been a little bit Nazis. We
just continue on this little train. No,
we try to change. We do better." Yeah.
We're trying to be nicer to the world.
That's great. So, French person. So, you
guys are together? Yeah. Where are you
from?
>> Mexico.
>> Mexico. Oh, there you go. This is like
the most likable and the least likable
for people right here. It's amazing. So,
you legal here.
[laughter]
Good. What about you? You also legal?
Just checking. Show me your paper. Show
me your paper. [laughter]
By the way, I love Mexicans. I just want
to say this. I love everybody. You know,
it's not like I'm not racist or
anything. I love There's only two things
I hate in this world. Racism and French
people.
Joking joke. I hate what's happening
with the deportations of Mexicans cuz
dude, we [__] need Mexicans. I love
Mexicans. If you get rid of Mexicans,
who's going to make Chinese food for
you? Okay. Who's going to do that?
[laughter] Who's going to make you feel
tall? Yeah. Who will do that?
Who's going to comfortably say the N
word besides black people? Right. It's
It's like the Mexicans. Yeah. All I'm
saying, if you want to make America
great again, don't deport Mexicans.
Deport the French. Yeah. Get [laughter]
I really got to stop making fun of
French people. It's too easy. Um,
let me talk about something else. Last
week had a pretty crazy week. I was in
New York and I was at a restaurant and
we're eating at the restaurant and the
table next to us, this guy was choking.
He was like I was like, "Oh my god, I
got to save him." So, I ran over. Okay.
I start pounding his back to save his
life. Then I realized he wasn't choking.
He was speaking French.
[laughter]
I love this so much. Also, did you know
that France is the only country in the
EU that has nuclear weapons? Why French
people? I feel like they're the most
likely country to nuke somebody out of
cuntiness.
>> [laughter]
>> If a leader of a foreign country is
going to dress in cargo pants, they're
going to be like, "Oh, his fashion
sucks." You know, [laughter] but I
wonder who decided that there was
probably a meeting with the UN and they
were like, "Hey, who wants to develop a
nuclear weapons program?" The Germans
were LIKE, "WE WANT IT. WE WANT IT."
Never mind.
We just build a recycling plant instead.
[laughter]
France can't have nuclear weapons. Cuz
if the Russians came to France, they
were like, "Okay, give us your nuclear
weapons." Then France will be like, "Oh,
oh, be our guest. Be our guest."
[laughter]
We don't want that.
>> It's a French shoe. Well, Shabbat
shalom. Now I can't hate you anymore.
Let's go.
>> You should have started with it. What do
you think about Japanese girls?
>> What
>> did you write that?
>> No, I didn't. [laughter]
>> My friend and editor Riley, shout out
just sent me a photo of this happening
in Japan. J-pop row. Sony apologizes for
Nazi outfits. So, it's these little
Japanese girls that dressed up as SS
soldiers with full swastikas. And in
Japan, like, do do you see that [__] all
the time? Like, are you guys familiar
with anime? There's like an anime I
watch where it's like these Japanese
girls, fully blonde Japanese girl,
portrays a German with like tanks just
rolling over like cities and [__] And
they really celebrate that [__] to a
concerning degree
cuz they're fighting with the Germans
like a second ago and now, you know,
it's very celebratory. Japanese girls.
Uh, love them. Yeah. Not in a weird way.
Just like I think they're cute. Yeah.
You know, a little Nazi, but [laughter]
Are you Japanese?
>> Chinese.
>> Chinese. Okay. What do you think about
the Japanese? By the way, [__] Japanese
people are the most hated people in
Asia.
>> My grandma wouldn't like them, but I I
love them.
>> You love them? Okay. Yeah, I get it.
Well, times have times have changed.
Yeah,
>> it's true. I mean, yeah. My grandpa also
didn't like the Jews, but
[clears throat] here we are. [laughter]
So, here we are. Times change. Yeah.
What do I think about Japanese girls?
Um, yeah. Kinky. Yeah. Uh, it's so funny
that Japan has this beautiful
connection. It's like the guilt kink
axis, right? Is axis funny cuz the more
guilt you have and the more oppression
you have and repression emotionally, the
more kinky you are. Have you noticed
that? Cuz Japanese people, a lot of
guilt, a lot of repression. Tentacle
porn. Huh? Just saying. Germany, a lot
of guilt, a lot of oppression. Techno
gang bangs on a Tuesday afternoon.
[laughter] That's what we connect on.
Both very bad in the soul. I think
there's a lot of um you know cuz Chinese
people are not that kinky.
[laughter] You are sir. This guy gives
me the darkest look. Okay. Okay. I get
it. Let's check out the Chinese glory
hole. What Pokémon would you be? Oh,
it's a good one. It's a great one. Do
you know the Pokémon names? They're
different in Germany than in America.
Gluak. Glu. Is that your favorite?
>> I like Turk.
>> Tok. That's great. Gluak. Do you know
Pokemon, sir? Do you know what Glac is?
Have a guess which which Pokemon it
would be?
>> Pikachu.
>> [laughter]
>> That's a good one actually. That's a
good one. That's actually not far from
the truth. Pikachu in German. [laughter]
No, the different names. Glag is
Charizard. It's a gland glutex.
They just become more German the more it
goes on, you know. And then my favorite
is Jigglypuff. In German, it's called
Pumalof. [laughter]
Pumalof. Cuz pum in German is like a
little fatty. We call him like, "Oh, so
Pumick." Yeah. A little fat. Look at
this little fat little kid there. He
just walking. He's a little pumy kid.
Yeah. And also Snorlax in German. called
Relaxo, right? It's so funny. And the
Pikachu is my favorite in German. It's
called
Very good. I'm kidding. It's Pikachu.
Very good.
>> What's your name?
>> Andreas.
>> Andreas. Is it a German name? What's
your last name?
>> No.
>> Oh my god.
>> Well, it's not educational. So, Andreas
derives from the Greek word Andreas,
which means the man.
>> Okay.
>> Now, now you can continue.
>> Thank you.
The fact that you just lectured me like
a country cut makes me think that you
are French. Actually, this is a French
person right here. I think you're more
French than anything. That was a little
bit of a German artist pouring through.
So, what makes you think that Americans
are dumb?
[laughter]
>> Like, what's the example? Is it like
>> necessarily think that they're
>> culturally limited?
[laughter]
Culturally limited.
Oh my god. That's the most that's the
most Cambridge way of dissing somebody,
dude. You know, you know, in Boston, we
would call that [__] you know?
[laughter] They're just culturally
limited. It's not their fault. They just
have not been outside of their bubble
yet. These little stupid fish, you know,
they just can't they
culturally I'm going to use that. That's
hilarious. [laughter] I love it. And
what made you move to America?
>> This man.
>> Oh, this man. Are you American? Are you
the culture limited? [laughter]
>> Oh no, it's getting worse and worse,
dude.
>> Bulgarian.
>> Oh, you're also Bulgarian.
>> He's got the citizenship.
>> How do you get your citizenship, sir?
>> Uh, that's
[laughter]
>> No, he's a little slow. He's just a
little culturally limited. Give him some
time. Okay, give him some time. He's
answering the question. Yeah,
>> you talked about having kids earlier. My
dad's Greek Jewish. My mom's
[laughter]
>> We always have one guy who ves for
whatever, you know, full on. Yeah. Greek
Jews. Yeah. Okay.
>> Well, there's lots of like 10,000 in
Greece now. So, that's that's weird. Um
>> 10,000 Jews in Greece.
>> Well, yeah, there's less then.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Cuz you guys killed them all.
[laughter]
>> Sorry. I I never thought I also feel
guilt towards Greek people. Now, this is
all of it. Okay. Well, sorry again.
Yeah.
>> Worse. One of them was my grandfather
who was 13 and three concentration
camps.
>> Oh, no.
>> He went to three concentration camps.
He's been around the block. What the
dude? Three? Oh my god. That's insane.
>> Oh god.
>> Cool. Okay. So, what's your question?
Can we get to the [__] question? Can
you just ask the [__] question now?
This was horrible. This was horrible
information you shared. Do you want to
ask me about my favorite castle or
something like that? [laughter]
>> Um, my mom, she's um Irish, Swedish, and
German.
>> And what did I do to her? What did we do
to What do we do to your Swedish mom?
>> No, but so she's like very German. She's
like her side is like very cold and his
side is very like warm and
>> bad. Yeah.
>> So like do you have any questions of
like what growing up like that was? Cuz
like that's what your kids are going to
grow.
>> So your question is if I have a question
for you. So you asked me and just made
me feel guilty for five minutes with
your monologue. And then you're like I
don't have a question but if you have
any questions for me then I'm here. I'm
here. I'm here. Oh my god. This is
horrible. You're manipulating me. You're
like typical Jew. Am I right? This is
horrible. Unbelievable. Unbelievable.
Playing Jedi mind tricks with me. This
is horrible. [laughter] Do you guys have
any questions for her? How about that?
>> Germans are the [__] of Europe.
>> Who sent a sperm test here, guys? Nobody
sent a sperm test. You did it, but you
seem more way more enthusiastic.
>> A black American. [laughter]
>> Mario, I couldn't buy a beer anywhere.
Whenever I went to a bar, people would
give me a beer. I was like, "Oh my god."
>> Why do you think that is? Do you think
we have I think here's also what it is.
I think we Germans we really try to be
better people right now after everything
we've done. So we have this
overcompensation and it like doesn't
only hit the Jew, it goes beyond Jews
and now maybe it also hit you. You know,
maybe it's some sort of reparation.
>> You know what it is? I figured it out.
You're not going to believe it cuz I met
a lot of German friends of mine that
are, you know, that are guys. And we
went to Holland.
>> Holland.
>> And we went to Belgium.
>> Okay.
>> And everybody [clears throat] hates the
Germans there.
>> Oh. [laughter]
POISONING MY BROTHER. THEY HATE me in
America everywhere. So that's why we get
along so great. Germans are the [__]
of Europe.
[applause]
>> Wow,
I'm going to start saying that.
>> [laughter]
>> the Germans are the Okay,
that is so crazy because okay, if your
argument is true that you know you
identify with the people who are the
most hated in Europe, I would argue if
that is your case right now because you
know you as a black person endure a lot
of racism and people hating you and
things like that for who you are and
where you're from. I would make the
argument that French people are the
nwords of Europe. Cuz let's be real,
dudes, nobody is hated more than French
people. Not only in Europe, I think in
the world. And this is the point where
I'm going to have to abort this [__]
because I don't know where to go from
here. I was going to did, bro, you also
deflected my question. Didn't we talk
about something else? Sperm. How the
[__] did we get [laughter] from a sperm
contest to you telling me that Germany
is the nword of Europe? Are you guys
football people here? My gods. That's
the Seattle Penguins. [__] [laughter]
right.
Go Birds is the gayish I've ever heard.
Go Birds. YOU SUPPORT THE BIRDS.
Go Birds. Oh my god. Football is the
gayest sport ever. And I'll say this
enough [laughter]
cuz people often say that soccer is such
a gay sport cuz I grew up playing soccer
my entire life. Dude, have you seen
American football? You have a white
receiver. Okay. Hello. [laughter]
A tight end. Are you kidding me?
My god. Listen. You cannot make fun of
soccer for being gay when your starting
position is this. Hey, Tom. You like
[laughter] this? Yeah. You like the
view, Tom? Yeah. Sorry. You're welcome.
[laughter]
I'm now going to pass you the ball
through my balls.
[laughter]
And then they're always like, "Okay,
Tom, you do something cool. You guys,
let's wrestle our [laughter]
Bill took me to my uh first ever
baseball game in Ohio. We saw the
Cleveland whatever the [__] team is.
Guardians." Yo, the team names are epic,
too, in America. New York Giants, Boston
Terriers. I love that [__] In Germany,
we don't have team names like that. My
favorite team in Germany, it's called
like what the [__] you know? And I went
to a baseball game. Walk in. First thing
I get, I got a Coors Light.
[laughter]
>> $17.
$17 for a Coors Light.
>> That sounds about right. Nothing about
that sounds right. $17. I thought what a
ripoff, but then I thought about it. I
was like, "Oh, maybe it's not a ripoff
cuz I can just piss in it and drink it
again. It tastes the [laughter] same."
Oh man,
it's just so funny. America is so [__]
politically cuz it's so divided here. I
hate the division that's happening cuz
the issue is that you only have two
parties in America. Create so much
division. In Germany, we don't have
that. In Germany, we either have seven
parties or one fug. Yeah. Either way,
[laughter]
either way, we're less divided. Cuz
here's the thing. This true story. Like
in in America, I feel like an opinion is
always linked to a party, puts you in a
box. In Germany, it's just an opinion.
Like in Germany, if you don't want to
get the vaccine, people are like, "Oh, I
think he does not like vaccines." Yeah.
Simple. In America, if you don't get the
vaccine, people are like, "Oh, I think
he hates trans people." [laughter]
The [__] Where did they come from? Any
other Europeans here? You got some?
Yeah. Where you guys from?
>> Germany.
>> Germany. Of course, we got Germany. Hell
yeah. You American?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Oh, yeah. Oh, [laughter] yeah. Big time.
All right. I'm a little turned on right
now by you. How American are you? Where
were you born?
>> Chicago, Illinois.
>> It's not American enough. It's not very
Cleveland, Ohio is the only acceptable
answer. Yeah. What's the toughest thing
about dating a German?
>> Oh god. [laughter]
>> Bread isn't bread, apparently.
>> Brett is not bread. That's right. No,
no, no, no, no, no. This is This is not
I'm I'm totally on her side with this,
you know. Don't try to relate to me.
American Wonderbread is an insult to
bread. Okay. He's not even trying to be
bread. It's unbelievable. So, you ate
Wonderbread and stuff growing up?
>> Peanut butter and jelly sandwich.
>> The peanut butter and jelly sandwich.
That's not People rave about that [__]
so much. I think it's like some weird
childhood kink y'all have. It's weird.
[laughter]
>> Also, your jelly is not even jelly.
American food. I love America. I love
America. [laughter]
Actually, [__] this place. Your jelly is
not jelly. Your bread is not bread. Even
the peanut. I don't know what's in
American food, dude. It's so funny.
Like, you look at American ingredient
list. It's wonder bread. It has 25
million ingredients including [__]
lactose and like some weird gum gelat
like it's rubber probably. You know what
I'm saying? A lot of Americans are I'm
not going to get the vaccine, which is
totally cool, but then you also cannot
eat ranch cuz you don't know what you're
putting in your body in any way. It's
like, you know what I'm saying? The
pretzel is absolutely pathetic. That is
a pretzel. Did you just order him a
pretzel? This is absolutely Sorry. Okay,
you're off the hook. You [laughter]
[__] [__] Yeah, you guys are the
trifecta of people who piss me off. You
know, [laughter]
American wonder bread over here. Little
French country and you cool. Actually,
the Dutch people we like. Yeah.
[laughter] My god. Enjoy eating your
soft ass [__] pretzel. Yeah. [laughter]
Have you been to Germany? Have you had a
real pretzel? Like a sex thing. That's
not like Have you had a real pretzel?
Show you a real pretzel. [laughter]
It's not sweet. That is good. Why would
a pretzel be sweet in the first place?
[laughter]
>> They have sweet pretzels. You culturally
appropriating [__] It's really bad.
>> [laughter]
>> Where are you from, sir?
>> Holland.
>> Holland. Oh, the Dutch people. Would you
agree that Dutch is objectively a more
[__] up language than German? It is,
>> right? Dutch people, they have
everything is guttural. It's like
it's insane. It's so much guttural
sounds. You all just had a better
history. So, nobody thinks of you that
way. Like, Hitler really [__] things
up for us. If you think about it, people
only think German is such an aggressive
language cuz of Hitler. If we didn't
have Hitler, Germany would be the
language of love. Maybe not. Maybe not
that. Maybe not [laughter] that. But I'm
just saying Hitler would make any
country scary. A Dutch Hitler. Imagine
Dutch Hitler with like a wooden shoes,
you know, [laughter]
little braids, you know, instead of a
mustache with a tulip. He's like,
"Hello, my name is Adolf Prince
Hitler and FIFA conquer dominate in you.
[laughter]
But first, get out of the bike lane.
Clink clink. That's crazy.
Do you find Orthodox Jewish appearances
amusing, strange? Do you see why Hitler?
[laughter]
>> All right, guys. That's our show. Thank
you so much for coming. [applause] No,
I'm kidding. I'll of course answer the
question. Okay. Uh, what the [__] was
that? This is crazy. Here's the thing
about the Jews.
[sighs]
We have so much guilt as Germans towards
Jewish people, but we also never met
Jewish people, you know, cuz there
aren't a lot of Jewish people in
Germany. Uh, so we have this guilt and
truly when I first came to America, like
I was afraid. Like we Germans were
afraid of Jews. Not because the horns or
the space laser or anything [laughter]
just because we're afraid that we're
going to meet Jewish people and that
they're going to hate us just because
we're Germans. And deep down we're even
more afraid that we might hate them. Cuz
that's worse cuz we don't know. We've
never met them. That's worse. Imagine
you're German. You meet a Jewish guy for
the first time in your life and after 5
minutes you're like, "Fuck, I get it.
Fuck." Like that's worse. [laughter]
Is that on sale? You're like, "Fuck,
Grandpa Ga was right." You know, we
don't want that. [laughter]
>> And your girlfriend is European,
>> Portuguese and British.
>> British and Portuguese? I don't know
what that that's crazy. You sound more
British than Portuguese, though. Is that
a choice you make? Do you want to sound
more British cuz people think it's
sophisticated? [laughter]
>> I lived in England my whole life.
>> Oh, you did live in England your whole
life. I learned this about America.
people when you have a hotline or
something, people fake a British accent
because people think that is more
sophisticated or implies a level of
intelligence, which is [__] hilarious
because I live in Europe. I know them.
You know, you look at British people
through the lens of James Bond and all
like Henry Kev, all these beautiful like
very smart British people, but I know
them and we know that England is the
Florida of Europe. It is. [laughter]
It is. I'm sorry.
>> I don't think so.
>> You would not agree. Where you from in
England?
>> Nottingham.
>> Nottingham. Okay. So you live in
Nottingham, which is a very specific
part of England. But once you leave
London, oh, it gets real ugly real
quick. You're very beautiful cuz you
came here. That's the thing. Like the
British [laughter] people who come to
America are hot, but the ones that
stayed,
I like them, but it's just a fact, you
know, they struggle with ugliness.
It's okay. That's why I think England
had so many colonies cuz they were like,
we got to do something about our people,
[laughter] you know? We got to like we
got to expand, right? Maybe they should
have colonized a dentist's office. I
don't know. Here's [laughter]
a fun fact about England. Allegedly, I
don't know if this is true. This might
be a myth, but the Vikings, right,
coming from Iceland, Norway, they
allegedly went to the UK and like were
plundering and pillaging and then they
took the hot British girls brought them
to Norway and look what's left in the
UK. That's what I'm saying. [laughter]
[applause]
You spent New Year's Eve in Berlin.
You have been to war, my friend. It's
insane. I was in the middle of Berlin
one year and there was a guy, you know,
you can buy like firecrackers, stuff
like that. And they buy the illegal [__]
from Poland. So Poland for some reason
has the best weapons like in terms of
like the not for this conflict obviously
they're useless, but for the
firecrackers. They have the biggest.
They don't care about any like gun laws
or something. You can buy grenades
legally in Poland. It's insane, dude.
And I saw this guy, he bought like this
Polish kind of rocket. And then this
dude, he broke the stick, put it on
fire, and then put the rocket into, you
know, like one of these rolls where you
carry paintings in almost like a pipe,
you know, put it in a pipe, held it like
a bazooka on Alexander Plat in Berlin.
And the thing just like fired all over
the place and just and probably killed
some innocent civilians. This is insane.
Berlin is wild. When I saw that [__] I
was scared. There's like things going
off left and right. I was like, I want
to go somewhere safer like Gaza. Jesus,
[laughter]
>> your football teams have such cool
names, you know, like Cincinnati
Bengals, like the Seattle Seahawks, the
Boston Terriers, you know, it just
sounds like a fire name. And you also
name teams after like Warriors, like,
you know, the Kansas City Chiefs. Yeah,
we Germans started doing that, too.
Yeah. Oh, Jesus. We don't like the
Chiefs.
>> Racist.
>> They're racist.
>> No, we don't give a about that. We just
hate them.
>> Oh, we hate them. Yeah.
>> But don't we hate them in the same way?
This going to be a little messy, but
stay with me. This is a very new analogy
I have. People don't like the Eagles,
right? But they were playing in the
Super Bowl last year. The Chiefs, they
won twice in a row. So then people were
even rooting for the Eagles. And that's
why I think what happened if World War
II broke out
because Germany, we lost twice. We're 0
and2. You know what I'm saying? And
America is 2-0. And everybody loves an
underdog story. [laughter]
So if you can like the Eagles, you may
you may like Germany and root for them.
I think we're going to be on the good
side of history this time. Hopefully.
>> How do we get there, dude? I didn't want
to. So, back to football. I have a whole
thing written about the football names,
but yeah. But no, the names are epic.
>> Native Americans.
>> That's what you mean. Not the players,
cuz you know. Okay. Okay. Because it's a
Native American head of Yeah. Yeah.
leader. Yeah. Chief. Yeah. Imagine
German had a team. The Frankfoot Furas.
Yeah. [laughter]
The Stoodgot Stormtroopers.
The Berlin Blitzks. Yeah. Okay. Why so
many Germans move to Spain if they're
the opposite of efficiency? It's Is it
from you Spanish people?
>> So, I don't know if
>> I don't know if Americans know this, but
so many Germans move over to Spain,
specifically a part called Mayorca,
which is now called Little Germany. It
is truly it is like we are going to the
17th German state. You understand? Like
we go to Mayorca, it is Germany now. The
most recent country Germany invaded is
Mayorca, Spain. Okay, we took it over.
Everybody speaks German there. The music
is so [__] German. There's no more
cha cha cha. There's none of that. It's
just all
shlook.
You know, it's like TICK TUCK TICK TUCK.
>> THAT'S RIGHT. IT'S all of that [__]
See, this is where [laughter]
tick tuck tick tucki.
>> I know where the Germans are. You guys
are [__] up. Isaac
>> n it was a test. It [laughter] was a
test. The two German. Oh my god. She
channeled the spirit of her forefathers
that came straight from the pit of your
soul. Oh my god. What's your name? You
probably have the most Germany. You like
Are you pri or something?
>> My mother is
>> Your mother is plea. See that's the
problem. She was very pleet. You have a
Jewish dad.
>> My whole family is Jewish.
>> Oh well Shabbat shalom. That's good. How
do you feel about this? You got you want
to sit over there and feel like this is
What is your name? Your mom's name is
Pittet. What is your name?
>> Iris.
>> Iris. Iris. It's a respectable German
name also. So you're from Germany in
this
>> clearly. That's good. Yeah. So you guys
are all friends, right?
>> No, we don't know each other.
>> You don't know each other? Just a group
in the in the center. Just you five
Germans just sitting in the middle of
the stage. [laughter]
>> Like six. This is the most German thing
you could have said. See that? Oh my
god. This is like German Karen at its
best. It's actually six. Get the facts
right. Mor. Yeah. So you Jewish and the
Jew the Jew in this group.
[laughter]
>> Did you just say she was Jew? Was that a
joke? Was that a German joke?
Oh, I thought she's the Jew of us. See,
there's like a [laughter]
>> cuz a group of six Germans always need a
Jew. Otherwise, it's in a little uh
[laughter] six Germans is too many.
Especially if one of them is named and
uh [laughter]
so no Jewish people in your group. Okay.
Well, we got to work on that. Yeah.
Maybe
>> adopt her.
>> You will adopt her with with consent,
please. Okay. We can you can't just take
her. We're done with that. We're done
just overtaking things and taking them.
No, no, no, no. We don't do this
anymore. That's what the Jews do
nowadays. You know what I mean? We're
done with that.
[laughter]
Okay. This is not how I intended the
show to start, by the way. I was
[laughter] like, But you all live in the
US now?
>> We work together.
>> Oh, you work together? Oh my god. Do you
work at the embassy or something?
>> Close.
>> Oh my god. Where do five Germans work
together? If you work as a German
America, you either work for the embassy
or you're in some deep sex techno rink,
you know, [laughter]
>> or maybe engineering. Engineering is
also very German.
>> Dominatrix, just like six dominatrixes.
>> She's Swiss and she's Dutch. So, they
don't count.
>> They don't count. They have to sit on
the far left. You know, these [laughter]
>> I get it. Okay. Yeah. You guys are the
core though. You guys are the Sikai core
of this group. Keeping the German
identity. I like that. Yeah. I've never
heard of a Dutch dominatrix.
[laughter]
How's your dominatrixing going? You just
go like, "Do you want a strooen buff?"
And then be like, "Please stop, stop,
please stop." You agree that Dutch is
objectively a worse language than
German, right?
>> I'm not sure.
>> It sounds so guttural. Like, how do you
say Burger King?
>> You hear that [__] Do you hear that
[__] She had a throat cancer just now.
Are you serious?
Come on, guys. This is messed up. up and
then everybody says, "Oh, we German.
Such bad vo," which of course of history
is way worse, but German is a cute
language. If we didn't have Hitler,
dude, German would be the language of
love.
>> Maybe not quite that, but you get my
point, right? It's not. So, what do you
do?
>> I'm a photographer.
>> What do you do photography of?
>> Uh, people
>> people
>> for magazines.
>> Let's go. Amazing. You know, I used to
be a male model.
>> I heard that.
>> Yeah. I I don't see it, but um
[laughter] I heard that there a little
German [__] over there. You see that
[__] I heard that. Yeah. It's good.
Thought I was going to be a big model,
too. I moved to New York for modeling
when I was uh 19 years old. I thought I
was going to be on a billboard for
Calvin Klein on Time Square. My first
paid modeling job, no joke, was for the
online catalog of Target, fully dressed
in a full body suit as a blueberry
muffin. [laughter]
[__] did it. Yeah, modeling [__] me
up, man. I was so broke as a model. Cuz
also, women in modeling make about three
times more than men for the same exact
job. You know about this? There's a pay
gap in America and we need to talk about
it. [laughter]
You seem like a very sweet guy. Cuz I'm
I'm going to be honest with you. I've
had a lot of very creepy situations with
photographers. I was in Milan, Italy one
time for fashion week. And this
photographer named Franchesco, he came
up to me and he was like, "Hey, Mario,
uh, I can shoot you for the cover of
Vogue magazine. But if you want to get
that, you have to let it be." [laughter]
No joke, this happened. And I was 19
years old. And, uh, I was I was very
confused, you know. I was like, "Uh,
hold on, Franchesco. You want to give me
a magazine cover and you want to give me
a [__]
Sign me the [__] up, [laughter] bro.
It's like a two for one. It's like a
Black Friday special. Happy holidays.
The magazine looked great, but I just uh
[laughter]
it was Vogue magazine, you guys. Okay.
It's a business decision at that point.
It's nothing to do with sexuality. It's
just smart business management. What's
more straight than good business
decisions? Yeah. It was weird though cuz
um he was so weird to talk about this,
but he was very he was very skilled.
Okay. I mean, no offense to any women,
but gay men are way ahead of the game
when it comes to [__] Yeah. And it
kind of [__] up the relationship with
my wife cuz sometimes, you know, I love
her so much, but sometimes I look at her
and it's just tough to know that no
matter how much I love her, she's never
going to be able to touch me the way
Franchesco did. [laughter]
She wants to give me a [__] but like
what? What am I getting out of this?
Huh? What is this? [laughter] Is it
Versace? Is it Prada? Huh? What are we
doing? Any Latinos here tonight?
>> You look 0% Latino. [laughter] Really?
You're so white, dude. You're more white
than me. I look more Latino. What is
your name?
>> Shane.
>> Shane? Are you [__] kidding me,
Shane? [laughter]
I could not come up with a wider name
than Shane.
>> Shane is your name?
>> There's never been a Latino named Shane.
Like, what is your name? Shane Gonzalez
Paredes. [laughter]
>> What's your last name?
>> Laguna.
>> Oh, there you go. Laguna.
>> Been a problem my whole life. My mom
told my dad, "Don't make him cry in
public because it'll look like you stole
him."
>> Oh, wait. So, Oh, that's good. That's
good. Okay. So, who's Latino?
>> My dad's uh Puerto Rican.
>> Your dad's Puerto Rican?
>> Yeah.
>> How are you so white, though? I got bad
news for you, dude. I feel like
[laughter]
>> How dark is your dad?
>> You know, decently
>> decently. [laughter]
>> Decently black. You know, not too black.
Have you ever done a 23 and me?
>> He's actually my dad. That's
>> He's actually your dad's. So, what's
your genetic breakdown?
>> Uh, it's like 6% actual Puerto Rican.
[laughter]
>> Six. What does he even mean? 6% is so
low. If you're 6% Puerto Rican, your dad
the maximum percentage of Puerto Rican
is 12%.
>> Well, he's also there's like some weird
mix of Africa in there.
>> Okay, cool. You're black. That's what
you're saying. [laughter]
>> You don't have enough swag to be black.
I'm sorry. Like you look like a
Patagonia sales rep or something. You
know,
>> do you know each other?
>> We're friends.
>> Friends? Okay. When you refer to him, do
you say, "Hey, that's Shane." My Puerto
Rican friends.
>> We're in school together. What do you
guys study?
>> Uh, toy design.
>> Toy design?
>> Yeah.
>> You're not black. There's no way.
[laughter] But
>> toy design. How many black people do you
work with
>> besides yourself?
>> Oh my god. Yeah. I got three black
friends who work at my thing. You know,
their names are Dylan, Cody, and uh
[laughter] I love it. Do you speak
Spanish?
>> Not in the slightest. No.
>> Not in the slightest. Your percentage
drops every second we talk. I feel like
you're less and less Latino. Yeah. Did
he show up on time today? Unfortunately,
>> you are not Latino. See, Latinos, they
would have been like, "Oh, whatever. The
comedy show always at 9:30. We just show
up whenever." Because we're Colombians.
You know that. My ex is Latina. That's
why I can say this cuz my ex Latina. She
was always so late. And it was a bit of
a cultural clash, right? Because I would
be like, "You're 20 minutes late." And
she always be like, "But Mario, I'm just
Colombian." I was like, "What the [__]
does that mean? [laughter]
I'm just Colombian. What a stupid
excuse." That's really [__] up cuz
you're basically saying that just
because your country historically does
something, you're going to keep going
with that and not try to change.
Imagine we Germans did that. Yeah.
Imagine. Imagine we're like, "Oh,
whatever." Yeah. We've always been like
this. We just continue on. Don't change.
We did better. So my people try to do
better. So Latinos, please do better.
That's right. Any other Latinos here
besides Shane? Like you look more
Latinos. What's your name?
>> Angel.
Um, Angel. So, you fully Americanized.
Anybody learning German here right now?
>> Learning.
>> Yeah. Right. Cuz I hear it a lot. Some
people come to my shows cuz they're
learning German, which is hilarious. If
you learn German from my videos online,
you're going to sound very gay and
aggressive at the same time. You go,
"Yum, yum."
Nice. So, how's it going with the German
learning?
>> It's fine. It's bad.
>> It's bad. It's fine. It's bad. See?
Yeah. So, why would you want to learn
German?
>> I think it sounds funny. [laughter]
She's not wrong. Right. So, you just
want to learn it so you can use it and
do like a fun goofy accent or
>> 100%.
>> Really?
>> And also, I'm Jewish, so I think it's
funny.
>> Yeah, that's very funny. Yeah.
[laughter] Yeah.
>> No, we also we Germans, we learn a lot
of Hebrew, too, cuz we think
[clears throat] it's hilarious. It's
like [laughter]
>> So, how does your family feel about you
wanting to learn German?
>> Well, only one half of them is Jewish.
So, my mom is I don't know. She doesn't
love it, but that's
>> So, your mom is Jewish. That makes you
for real. For real, Juju. For real. For
real.
>> Yeah. Cuz my wife, her dad's Jewish. Her
mom's not Jewish. So, she's not juju.
Jewish.
>> She's not Jew. She's not Jewish. Trust
me, she is. I didn't know she was
Jewish. At first, I saw her one night. I
was waking up in the middle of night.
She was in the kitchen. She was uh
sacrificing the blood of Christian
babies. I was like Jewish, [laughter]
you know. I didn't know.
Kidding. She was doing taxes and then I
was like, "Oh, she's [laughter]
Jewish here."
[cheering]
Amazing. I was going to say, "Use your
left hand, but you can do that. That's
fine."
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, this is the most Jewish people
I've ever seen in the room. This is
amazing. Usually when there's a German
speaking in front of large crowds, there
aren't that many Jewish people. Uh but
uh things must be going pretty bad when
you need a German to come in for comedic
relief. Uh [laughter]
do you have the word douchebag here in
the UK? What do you say here?
>> That feels I shouldn't have said it
feels You sound like a frog right now.
What the [__] is this language? TWA. I
didn't even know that was a bad thing. A
[__] A [__]
>> [__] I never forget. There's a bunch of
British people correcting me. [__] It's
a [__] It's [__] Not [__] It's [__]
You have to get it right. Do one more
time. Yeah. So, what does that mean? A
[__] A vagina. That's not a bad I'm a
vagina man. I I take it. Yeah. I like
being a vagina man. Yeah. You just call
dudes a vagina. That's cool. TW.
Jesus [__] Christ. I'm German. Okay.
You cannot pronounce folkswagen
correctly. to come with me with this
twice twice. Say right. Okay. I'm sorry
I mispronounced your slurs. Uh so I went
back to Germany, back to
and um
[laughter]
that's right. Yeah. Is something funny
about my hometown? Yeah. You have a
street called Schlomi Boulevard or
something. You have the Schmeckle Street
or something like that. Yeah. Yeah.
Where are you from?
>> Poland.
>> Poland. Never mind. Yeah. [laughter]
Well, [__] a sorry for the invasion.
Yeah, I guess we have like a This is
rough. Yeah. Does Polish sound just as
aggressive as Russian, would you say? Or
is it a little bit
>> less, right? Cuz Russian is like from
Polish people say vodka. Russian say
vodka. Like vodka.
>> If you're Russian, you have pet names
for inanimate objects like vodka or
cabbage.
>> That's so cute. That's amazing. I'm just
picturing like a Russian soldier
invading Ukraine and give me my
man. I respect Russians less now. That's
cool. Yeah. See, that's we need to know
that cuz Russians, we think of them as
these scary people, but they're cute,
too. You're German, I'm assuming.
>> Half German. You look full German,
though. I mean, I don't know what to
tell you. Everything about you is so
quintessentially German. I couldn't even
make it up, bro. I mean, the Bayern
Munich had the Germany jersey, which is
a bold move in the UK. It's a bold move.
And then even your socks are German, and
you have shorts on, which is the most
German thing of them all. Glad you don't
have his mustache cuz otherwise you'd
have a problem. But this is good. Yeah.
You know, I like soccer, you know,
supporting Germany and soccer. It's just
weird with national pride in Germany cuz
I walked around here, you all have a lot
of flags, like British flags everywhere,
which, you know, I'm very jealous of cuz
in Germany we don't have any German
flags. We don't really have national
pride in Germany cuz we used to have a
little bit too much. See, in the UK, you
guys have pride month. In Germany, we
have guilt year. Okay. Every year, you
know, in Germany, you can either be an
engineer or a techno DJ. You German.
engineer.
>> ANDREW, [laughter]
>> I [__] YOU. LOOK AT THAT. SEE WHAT
I'M [__] I don't know this person. I
don't know him. I just You have engineer
vibes. So, what do you engineer?
>> It This is the most German answer.
Americans are going to be like, they
tell me their whole life story. You
know, I've been doing it for 7 years.
This guy is like it. [laughter]
Next question.
Was it always your first choice or were
you going to be a techno DJ in another
life? It again. IG. I love this guy.
He's the most German ever. What's your
name, sir?
>> Tom.
>> Tom. That's the most efficient name.
[laughter]
Every answer had maximum three letters.
Tom, it t and Tom. I like Tom. Do you
live in London, Tom?
>> Almost.
>> Almost. [laughter]
Almost.
>> What is your name?
>> Sylvia.
>> Usula. I didn't know that name existed
except for in Disney movies. That's so
funny cuz Usula Usula Ursula is Isn't
that the Disney the Little Mermaid? The
the bad fish. You're named after a bad
fish. [laughter]
You're evil fish. That's so funny. Do
you know that Disney fairy tales are
very different in the original German
version? So, The Little Mermaid is
actually I think The Little Mermaid is
from uh Denmark, but the European fairy
tales are so [__] dark. But then
Disney changed the original version cuz
American kids cannot handle the truth.
Okay. So, the Little Mermaid, she's
singing and then she she can't speak
anymore. Goes on land. The prince falls
in love with her. They defeat the sea
witch. Everything's happy. So, now in
the European version, this is what
happens. The Little Mermaid goes to
Usula and she goes, "Yo, I'd like to go
on land." And then Usula is like, "Okay,
we can make that happen. The only thing
we have to do is cut your tongue out
with a knife." So, she cuts the tongue
off with a knife, right? Then she grows
legs and then she goes on land, right?
But it's not like she can just walk like
a normal person. No. So, she walks on
land and every step she takes, it's like
a thousand knives stabbing her leg. This
is what what it says verbatim in the
story. And then she goes and meets the
prince to seduce him so he can fall in
love with her and everything's happily
ever after. And when she meets the
prince, the prince looks at her, goes,
"Nah, I'm good." Reject her. And then at
the end of the story, she jumps off a
cliff, turns into seafoam, and dies. And
that is the end of the story. And I
think it's such a beautiful story
because it teaches kids a lesson that
you should not dream. and have dreams
and go somewhere else. No, you stay
where you are. You do engineering. Yeah.
You don't move. [laughter]
You don't move to America to start a
dominatrix rink with your co-workers.
No, you stay in your lane. You do
engineering in Germany. And you are a
good boy. Because if you dream, you
might die. And this is a beautiful
story. And this is explains a lot about
European culture, why we're a little bit
more, you know, we have these hardcore
German fairy tales called Peta. You know
about pita? Oh, that shit's incredible.
For all the non-Germans, it's a little
collection of children's stories and
they're incredibly valuable for kids to
learn about life. There's one story
about a little girl named Palian. Yeah.
Pintian, she's playing with the matches
in her home and she's not supposed to.
And the cats, they yell at her. They're
like, "Meow meow." Pintian, do not play
with the matches. Your father told you
not to play with them. But Palinian is a
kinky bad girl. She doesn't give a [__]
Yeah. She does not listen. Yeah. So, she
starts playing with the matches. And
then in the next frame, Palinian is
burning. Yeah. Her whole dress is
burning. Her hair is burning. She's
screaming in excruciating pain.
[laughter]
But then luckily there's a huge twist
because at the end she dies. She's dead.
She's dead. Yeah. The end. It's a
beautiful story. Yeah. But guys know the
story actually does have a happy ending
because uh she never disobeyed her
father again. Yeah.
One less white girl who does not listen.
Yeah. It's a beautiful ending and I
think it's good. I've done that.
>> You've burned yourself or what? You've
you've read that book?
>> No, not literally, but when I was young,
my mom said the same thing. Don't use
the matchick. Put the house on fire.
>> You put the house on fire? No way. You
really did. Oh my god.
>> Because like sometimes the matchick
takes a bit longer.
>> You shouldn't make excuses now. You
should have listened to your parents.
Look at her trying to make excuses.
Yeah, but you know, I didn't follow the
rules, but it was very long matchix. It
happens to the best of us. Like you were
trying to relate to us. Do you see that
[__] She's trying to relate to us.
She's like, "Because you get it." You
know, sometimes the matches are long.
Sometimes the house burns down a little
bit. We've all been there. [__] So,
where is your mom from?
>> Uh, from India.
>> From India. Cuz Indians and Germans have
some similarities. Engineering, you
know, that's the one thing that brings
us together. But the Indian mom's got to
be a little bit more tough, I think.
Yeah.
>> It's similar.
>> Every question that we ask is answered
nine.
>> Nine. in German. Your Indian mom is like
your Indian
999. And did your mom ever tell you she
loves you?
>> No. [laughter]
>> Good. See, at least she didn't do that.
Yeah. That's why you're a strong woman.
But the house burning is like, you know,
I got to work on that. Yeah. So, how
many house you burnt down? One.
[laughter]
One. Just one. Good. Yeah. Yeah. Good.
Yeah. Nine houses. That's right. Jesus
Christ. I've been awakened people here,
dude. You know, behind you, the Asian
girl, she's like, "No, I told her to do
a full German. It's hilarious." Oh my
god. What did your Indian mom do as a
repercussion when you burned down the
house?
>> She just slapped me.
>> She slapped you.
>> Okay. Okay. Well,
>> that's very Indian thing.
>> That's a very Indian thing. You slap
>> your daughters. Okay, cool. Okay, cool.
Yeah. How old were you when you burned
down the house?
>> Four or five.
>> Four or five. Okay.
I hate that we have a little bit more
empathy for her now, do we? Uh, it's not
as funny now with empathy. I don't like
empathy. [laughter]
But again, a German four or 5year-old
who read his entire life. Truly, when
you when you read those stories as a
kid, it stays with you, you know. I
think there's something about that.
Yeah. Cuz Indians do not feel they don't
seem like obedient people in any kind of
way. My aunt just went to India for like
a spiritual retreat. The traffic is
unbelievable. Everybody jaywalks.
There's no rules. Even the cars, even
the cops jaywalk. It's uh Yeah, it's so
weird. You Indian people have no
discipline but then you have the best
engineers. It is really it's it's really
funny. You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
>> My whole family is engineers.
>> And what do you do for a living?
>> Film making.
>> Film making. So you are [laughter] okay.
>> Your mom is probably more mad at the
fact that you're a filmmaker. The fact
that you burnt down a house, you know.
She was like the house I get. But the
film making come on be an engineer.
Well, I think Yeah. Are you guys dating?
>> No.
>> No. Do you do you know anybody here? You
came by yourself?
>> I mean we came together but we are not
together.
>> Okay. You're not together. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
>> Yeah. You look so sad, bro. You look
[__] You look You look defeated as
[__] man. You like don't even know what
to say, dude. It's so funny. [laughter]
No, you are beautiful. I think you know,
but I think you have that going for you.
Uh yeah, that's interesting. I don't
know what to tell you. I know to tell
you. Yeah. Well, listen, you're a
filmmaker, but you seem like a great
person. I I forgive you uh for the house
burning down. Yeah. Give it up for her.
She shared her whole childhood with us.
Yeah. This is amazing. I'm going to
finish with my closing bit, which is
fire. Okay. I was going to say gas. No,
I'm kidding. Uh, it's too low. No, I I
was going to say it, but then I was
like, no. Uh,
>> how subconscious do you do you get when
you call a guy?
>> Say that one more time in English. No, I
love you. Act. Where you from?
>> Italy.
>> Italy. That sounded Russian. I thought
Russian. You were Italian with no
emotion. What happened? Cuz Italians ARE
USUALLY LIKE
THE ITALIAN. BUT YOU HAVE ITALIAN with
like you're like down there. No. No.
What's your question, sir?
>> The question is as a German.
>> Now I hear it. I HEAR
>> SOMETIMES WHEN I'M IN LONDON, I'M
CALLING A CAB. I DON'T WONDER LIKE, you
know, IF I WAS GERMAN, I would feel
self-conscious. [laughter]
>> Yeah. Yeah. I have a friend. I was in
New York with my Jewish friend Adam and
he was like, "Mario, why don't you just
hail a cap?" I was like,
>> [laughter]
>> So I walk up to the side of the road,
you know, my right arm is trembling. I
hear the German national anthem kicking
in.
I was like, "No, no, no. I can't do it.
I can't do it." Listen, it's only 7
miles. Let's just walk. Let's take a m
But at the end of the day, people always
ask me about the whole situation,
Israel, Palestine. I think we just need
to come together as people because it
doesn't matter if you're German,
Palestinian, Israeli. I think if we came
together, right, showed more empathy and
came together, Palestinians, Israelis,
Germans, if we came together, we can
easily take over France. Just saying.
Just saying. Right. Just saying. It's a
solution. Yeah. Not a final solution.
Just [laughter]
Just a solution. And then the
[clears throat] Palestinians could live
in France and then France won't even
change that much.
All right, guys. You're amazing. Thanks
so much for coming. I love you.
>> [music]